Miss!
Nice lady!
Excuse me,
I'm sorry to interrupt, but it looks like...
the lady you were with just left.
Mind your own business and get back to work.
Right. Of course.
Nice lady!
Hold on. Nice lady!
Nice lady.
Nice lady!
First, I think we should review the successful cases...
of the government rehabilitation support programs.
Also,
Eun Seol agreed to help with this scholarship program.
- Ms. Ko Eun Seol? - Yes.
Eun Seol herself...
is a successful case of the rehabilitation program.
When it comes to things like the necessary programs...
or the benefits of the project,
she'd know better than anyone else.
(Cheongma Scholarship Foundation, Chairman Kim Jung Sun)
You should take that.
Hello.
Director Joo, Ms. Park got into an accident.
What? An accident?
Got it. I'll be right there.
Wait, was that Hae Ra?
An accident? What happened?
It seems So Yeon got into an accident.
Wasn't she out shopping with Hae Ra?
How badly is she hurt?
Please calm down first. I'll go check on it.
Sure, I'll be there with Young Hoon.
What happened?
Kang Hae Ra.
I asked what happened.
I don't know. I don't know why I did that.
I just...
It just briefly crossed my mind.
For a second, I wanted her...
to disappear somewhere.
Tell me in a way I can understand.
Ms. Park hates my guts,
but she's everything to Seok Jin.
So I wanted her to disappear.
While I was picking out clothes,
she went outside as if she was possessed.
I thought if I just looked the other way,
Ms. Park would disappear somewhere.
That's why I didn't go after her.
But I didn't know she'd get into an accident like this.
I mean it.
Did you contact Chief Cha?
No. Not yet.
Contact him right away.
Listen.
This was just an accident.
This didn't happen because of anything you did.
If you act this anxious,
Chief Cha will notice right away.
Calm down and contact him right away.
Once the revised sample is confirmed,
the first mass production line has to be fully operational.
Right, I'll check the schedule.
Hey, Hae Ra.
What?
Okay, I got it.
Is something wrong?
My mom got into an accident.
Oh no, is she badly hurt?
I need to go. Please wrap things up here.
- Seok Jin, hey. - Mom.
Mom?
Seok Jin...
I think she sprained her arm a little when she fell.
What about...
Is she hurt anywhere else?
She wasn't hit directly by the car.
Thankfully, it just looks like bruises.
She seemed very shocked, so they gave her a sedative.
Chief Cha, you must be shaken.
But it doesn't seem like she's seriously hurt,
so that's a relief.
Exactly.
You can't leave a sick person unattended for even a second.
Chief Cha.
Hey, honey.
I've already spoken to the hospital director,
so they'll move her to the VIP ward.
A single suite is more than enough.
Just do as you're told.
I play golf with the hospital director here.
I've also arranged for a caregiver,
so keep that in mind.
Thank you.
Well,
you must have had quite a scare today,
so go on in.
So Yeon should wake up any second now.
Right.
- Let's go. - Okay.
I'll stay a little longer.
Right, sure thing.
(Cha Seok Jin)
Is your mother okay?
Hey.
Seok Jin.
Is your mother doing okay?
Yes, thankfully it wasn't a major accident.
She just hurt her arm a little.
Still, she must've been so shocked.
Yes, I think that was the case.
I'm sure you were really shaken up too.
I'll make sure to visit her when I have time.
I'd appreciate that.
My mom will really like it too.
Right. I'll see you at work then.
Seok Jin.
I'm sorry.
This is all on me.
It couldn't be helped. It was an accident.
But...
I really want to get along well with her.
So I was trying my best.
You're really disappointed in me, aren't you?
No.
This would've happened even if she was with me.
Thanks for understanding, Seok Jin.
I'll do better.
To you,
and to your mom.
I'm home.
Hae Ra.
Come here and sit down for a second.
Oh, boy.
Hae Ra,
are you sure you can handle being with Chief Cha?
What do you mean by that?
This incident must've made you realise...
what kind of guy the man you chose actually is.
He's already so rigid,
and he has a sick parent on top of that.
Are you prepared for that?
Why would you ask me that, Dad?
Did you date Mom fully prepared from the start?
Kang Hae Ra.
You know I'm right.
Mom's family couldn't even compare to yours.
Were you able to handle them from the beginning?
You just endured it because you loved her.
I will endure it all, too.
Hey.
Honey.
Please understand her.
Hae Ra likes Chief Cha a lot.
What can we do when our daughter's crazy about him?
All we can do is support them.
Chief Cha...
I'm just not entirely happy with him.
He's too rigid and lacks flexibility completely.
Maybe it's due to his background,
but he's driven in a negative way.
I actually like Chief Cha.
He kept his principles despite his difficult background.
And above all, he takes care of his sick parent.
Seeing him bear all the responsibility...
makes me feel proud, yet sorry for him.
I also like that he's upright and uncompromising.
You're unbelievable.
We always have completely opposite points of view.
That's why we were drawn to each other.
But you know what?
Looking closely at Chief Cha,
he strangely resembles you.
Me?
Yes. You've softened up over time,
but in your younger days, you were every bit as rigid...
and uncompromising.
No one was a bigger perfectionist at work.
Sometimes when I look at Chief Cha,
I feel like I'm looking at a younger version of you.
Is that so?
So, did anything happen with Chief Cha?
He understood.
Did you play your part?
Yes, thankfully it went smoothly.
It's unfortunate that So Yeon got hurt,
but this incident...
must've made Chief Cha clearly realise his place.
What do you mean by that?
Even the CEO stepped up today to take care of So Yeon.
You think so?
We need something more concrete to lock in Chief Cha's feelings.
What would that be?
By the way, you two promised to get married,
but you don't even have matching rings?
I want to get them,
but he isn't into the idea.
He hates making people feel burdened or something.
It'd be good to make a clear statement this time.
If you make your relationship with Chief Cha public...
using couple rings,
the CEO will accept him as his future son-in-law.
Joo Ae Sook, have you been well?
It's me. Your husband, An Guk Cheol.
Boss, I need to use the restroom.
How many times has it been today?
Gosh, don't ask.
Did something I ate yesterday go bad?
Wait, do you think you have food poisoning?
I doubt it.
I mean, how can you eat perfectly good food...
and get an upset stomach?
Peculiar, right?
What did you eat?
My dad cooked yesterday for the first time in ages,
and this happens sometimes when I eat his food.
Who usually cooks? Your grandmother?
That would be a disaster.
My grandmother is widely known to be a terrible cook.
Don't tell me you make Eun Seol do it.
We have a conscience, you know. How could we make her cook?
She's the sole breadwinner for the family right now.
We always ate well when my mom was still alive.
Her cooking was amazing.
But ever since she passed away,
we just make do with whatever we have.
If my grandmother's spending the day with her friends,
what am I going to eat?
Then come over to my place after closing.
What?
Wait, really?
A rehabilitation program for prison inmates?
Yes. Instead of a program that just hands out scholarships,
I'm planning a true social giveback program...
that gives young people a second chance.
Honey, the scholarship foundation program...
is first and foremost...
about improving our corporate image.
To build public trust,
we don't need to take on a risk like this.
Why bother supporting such individuals...
- Hey, Seok Jin. - Come on in.
- Have a seat. - Goodness.
How's your mother doing?
She'll be discharged in three days, but she'll only require light rehab.
Well, it's a huge relief it wasn't any worse.
Thanks to Hae Ra being there,
she was able to get to the hospital quickly.
Right.
And this.
I appreciate all that you did for us.
Thank you for getting my mother a hospital room.
I prepared a small gift for the holidays.
- Oh, my. - What is this?
They say it's good for managing blood sugar after meals.
Goodness, thank you.
My husband needs to start watching his blood sugar now, too.
Why don't we try it? You should have one, too.
- I'll have one. - Let's try one each.
Here.
- Is it one pill per serving? - Yes, that's correct.
I see.
This is nice. It's easy to take.
The moment I had it,
I could smell a hint of pine.
It was really fragrant.
Chief Cha, you're always so thoughtful.
Please don't forget to take them after your meals.
- Chief Cha. - Yes?
While your mother's in the hospital,
please let me know if you need anything at all.
I'll speak to the hospital director.
Right, thank you.
(Ildong Investigation Services)
An Guk Cheol?
You have to find him as soon as possible.
You know...
I mean, just look at this.
With only this basic personal info to go on,
it's bound to take both time and money.
I don't care what it costs.
Just find out every detail about his past.
Oh, my.
Seeing you this worked up,
makes me think...
Is he an ex-boyfriend who ran off with your money?
Watch your mouth and just do what you're told!
Right, of course.
I'll get right on it.
As always, you're the last one to leave.
Did everyone go to lunch?
Yes.
Let's grab lunch, too.
What should we get?
I'm sorry, but I have plans during lunch today.
Oh, really?
What can you do? Either way, there's always tomorrow.
It must be something important.
Yes, there's someone I need to see.
What? Nice lady, hi.
Are you feeling okay?
I'm okay.
Yesterday,
I banged right into a car.
My arm hurts a bit, but I'm fine.
That must have hurt a lot.
I'm okay.
You know,
I actually saw you that day.
What?
I thought it was you, so I ran after you.
That's how I got hit by the car.
Really?
Yes. But it's okay. Everything's fine.
By the way, nice lady,
do you want some orange juice?
No, I'm good.
Anyway, what's that?
Oh, this?
I thought you might be bored alone.
So I brought this. Do you like it?
Gosh, I love colouring books.
No way. It's so pretty.
I'm going to colour the dress pink.
Sounds good.
- Isn't it pretty? - It is.
What are you colouring that in with?
This one? Green.
- How about sky blue? - Sky blue? I like it.
(Planning Director, Cha Seok Jin)
Are you busy?
Yes, the opening event is coming up real soon.
Even if you're busy, can you look at me for a second?
Sure.
Ta-da.
What's that?
What else? It's one of our couple rings.
Usually, the guy is supposed to do this.
You know that, right?
Thank goodness it fits perfectly.
I told you I didn't need a ring.
I'm not just telling you to wear it. There's a reason for it.
What reason?
This will just make the employees uncomfortable.
They already know what kind of relationship we have,
so is there a need to go this far?
Just wear it, will you?
It's all because of my dad.
We have to do at least this much so he knows how serious we are.
He needs to know so he'll accept us.
Don't you want my dad's approval?
So don't take it off and always wear it.
Got it?
Mom, it's me.
Hey, Mr. Seok Jin.
What are you up to?
I'm going to colour all of this today.
Isn't it pretty?
What is this?
Don't you know what a colouring book is?
Where did you get it?
The nice lady gave it to me.
The nice lady?
Yes.
The nice lady thought I might be bored,
so she gave it to me as a gift.
When did the nice lady come by?
She came by earlier today.
No way, how is this possible?
How can everything be so delicious?
It's delicious, right? My mom is seriously the best cook.
She's seriously the absolute best.
Teun Teun, hurry up and dig in.
I didn't want to eat today,
but seeing you eat made me super hungry.
- I want some too. - Right, go ahead.
What...
Boss, you really have magic hands for cooking.
Seriously. You have a magic touch.
It's so precious.
What the...
Boss, if it's okay with you,
could I please have one more bowl of rice?
Why is he making a fuss holding my hand?
You're helping the Chairman with the new scholarship program?
Yes, I plan to help out as much as I can.
I know you mean well,
but I'm a little concerned.
Given the nature of the scholarship program,
people are bound to dig into your past.
Is there a need to voluntarily wear the Scarlet Letter?
I don't look at my past as a Scarlet Letter.
Besides, hiding my past isn't going to erase it.
It's unfair that I spent ten years in prison after being framed,
but that's all the more reason I need to show them...
I didn't break...
after enduring something like that.
And for someone out there,
I think my story could become a source of hope.
Eun Seol, you're much stronger than I thought.
I worried for nothing.
Gosh, no.
I didn't know you'd care for me this much, Ms. Joo.
Of course I care. You're my friend's daughter.
If only for Hee Jung's sake, I should care at least this much.
Thank you, Ms. Joo.
If you need help in the future, feel free to contact me anytime.
And keep me posted on the progress of the scholarship program.
I'm sure there will be things I can help with from the side.
Sure.
I wanted to get something a bit more flashy,
but Seok Jin doesn't really enjoy the attention.
Still, I'm planning on getting a luxury wedding ring,
something as flashy and noticeable as possible.
No matter how fancy the ring is,
if the person wearing it lacks sincerity,
what's the point?
It'll get in the way for no reason.
What? It'll get in the way?
Hey, do you even have a ring like this to be saying that?
If your feelings are real, is there any reason to show it off?
Whatever.
Right.
See, it has to be at least this good.
I can do this much, too.
Everyone learns off the internet these days.
All you have to do is follow the recipe.
Mom, that only works for people who actually have a feel for it.
You need to know how to season food properly.
People like us have to get out there and at least put in the legwork.
Fortune favours those who help themselves, remember?
Knock, and the door will be opened.
What if knocking doesn't work?
Then you keep knocking.
Eventually, they'll open the door just to shut you up.
Put in the effort.
You talk too much. Effort, my foot.
Do you think you'll hit the jackpot if you try hard enough?
Who said anything about a jackpot?
The core value of the Cheongma Scholarship Foundation...
goes beyond simple financial support.
It's about helping youth with potential...
grow into the leaders of our society...
by laying the groundwork to nurture future talents.
Joo Mi Ran?
I only know that she's doing well at some large company.
Oh, really?
I heard she changed her name.
To Joo Mi Ran, I believe.
Oh, my gosh. I hit the jackpot!
What? The jackpot?
What? No, it's nothing.
Why did you suddenly jump up while eating?
You startled me.
(Cheongma)
Getting couple rings...
means they're officially announcing...
their relationship, right?
That's right.
People get them when they want to show off...
that they're officially together.
Why? Did someone get matching rings?
What?
Who got them?
You know, people from work.
They must've wanted to end their secret relationship.
Cheongma's survival this season depends on the launch of Shoejoy.
If we don't meet the expectations of the buyers...
and the board of directors during the evaluation,
we won't have a future.
There's no room for error here.
With these evaluation results,
I'm going to prove that your trust in me...
was justified, sir.
Did everyone hear that?
Since Chief Cha is that confident,
the rest of the executives here had better watch closely.
Let's see whether his words are pure bluff,
or if he actually has what it takes to lead Cheongma into the future.
I made a reservation at a great restaurant for lunch.
Sounds good.
- Hello. - Hello.
(A Trap Called Desire)
Write down all the businesses or shops you want to run.
Who knows? We might win the lottery someday.
Why don't we start preparing for our wedding?
If you're going to marry me,
you need to get used to those kinds of gatherings.
People who are born with a servile mindset...
are just beyond saving.
Ko Eun Seol always bothered me.
You can't ignore the environment someone was born and raised in.
Things are urgent,
so we need to move up the interview dates.
Just you wait, Joo Ae Sook.
I'll soon bring you your biological daughter.
For our Eun Seol,
I need to step up and be a proper grandmother.